A long time ago, in an era where
there was no concept of 'shinobi',
in an attempt to end an era of violence,
a certain someone ate a forbidden fruit
and gained the power of chakra.
However, as time passed, they
became obsessed with that power.
To bring justice to the world,
what is it that we need?
Power or love?
This question would start an arduous war...
which has continued throughout the generations.
Hey, if you're a Hyuga show us your Byakugan!
If you can't don't show your face around here!
Your eyes are really creepy.
I bet you're actually a monster, right?
You Byakugan monster!
What's your problem?
The 'future hokage'?
Are you some kind of moron?
Take that!
We really taught this guy a lesson!
What's up with this "future hokage"?
For being so cocky, let's take care of his red scarf!
If it's the end of the world,
I wish meat would fall instead of the moon!
This is the Hyuga's...
...reply!
Naruto-senpai!
You say 'steak'?
Thank you very much.
Thanks for the food!
RINNE FESTIVAL
Naruto-senpai!
Please accept my Rinne Festival present.
I'm always cheering for you!
I made it myself!
Please accept it!
Thank you very much.
Coming up!
Five orders?!
I can't eat five more orders.
Naruto-senpai!
Thank you so much!
Over here, Senpai!
Let's eat together!
Order ready!
Coming!
Senpai, the gyoza are ready.
Let's eat!
If it's the end of the world,
I wish meat would fall instead of the moon!
Look, the moon.
The match up for the round seven...
Uzumaki Naruto vs.
Inuzuka Kiba.
Ninja Art Beast Mimicry: All-Fours jutsu.
Here I come.
Naruto-kun is fighting Pain right now.
Banshō Ten'in.
Soon I will take you with me.
If it's the end of the world,
I wish meat would fall instead of the moon!
Uzumaki Naruto.
Senpai, the gyoza are ready.
Let's eat.
Senpai.
Uzumaki Naruto.
Roger.
Hurry up and move forward!
I can't go any further!
Hey, stay in the line!
Keep calm. Please keep calm.
Hinata-sama, welcome to the castle.
Welcome.
Hinata-sama, only those of exalted status
are allowed to see the real Tenseigan.
This is a temple where those
of lower rank come to pray.
Raikage-sama, the Chakra Cannons are ready.
Yes sir.
Pulverize. Powderize!
Roger!
The Sixth Gate Of Joy!
Damn it!
The meteorites are gone.
Hokage-sama.
Hiashi-san?
Chakra capacity at 75%
76, 77...
Chakra capacity at 95%
96, 97, 98, 99...
Chakra is at 100%
Yeah!
Chakra capacity at 90%
Hokage-sama!
Hiashi-san would like to speak with you.
Do not destroy the moon...
I'm certain that Hanabi and Hinata are there.
Chakra capacity at 95%
Raikage-sama, an urgent
message from Hokage-sama.
I can't shoot at Naruto.
Raikage-sama, there is
something written on the moon...
Kurama is writing something on the moon's surface.
Snowball fight?!