Long ago, back when the concept of shinobi did not exist.
A certain person bit into the forbidden fruit,
and obtained the power of chakra...
...and tried to end the age of violence.
However, in time, They become obsessed with power.
To maintain order in this world,
does one need power or love?
This conflict would
spark a long war,
that continued through into
the generations that followed.
If you are Hyuuga's daughter, just show me your Byakugan.
If you don't want, don't look us here.
Your eyes are creepy.
I'll bet your actually a monster, right?
Yeah, you Byakugan monster.
Hey, stop!
Huh, who are you?
I'm Uzumaki Naruto,
the future Hokage.
Future Hokage?
Don't be stupid.
Be prepared.
Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
影分身の術
(Kage Bunshin no Jutsu: "Shadow Clone Technique")
Huh?
I'll beat you.
So will I.
Take this!
He's weak.
The future Hokage bullshit!
Don't act so cool.
I'm not done yet!
This time, I'm gonna show you an awesome technique.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
They've runied your scarf.
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
W-wait!
Thank you very much.
See ya.
If the world were to end tomorrow.
Who would you like to spend your last day with?
Like that would happen.
Just suppose,
the moon began to fall.
If it's the end of the world,
I wish meat would fall instead of the moon.
If the moon began to fall, I will protect you.
No, thanks. I don't need to be protected by you.
Write down who you'd want to
spend your last day on Earth with.
Ah, It's impossible.
I don't know what my father's name,
my mother's name,
and I don't have any friends.
Hey, Naruto.
Don't throw out your paper.
But, it is unlikely the world will end,
I'm just saying "if" it does.
Well, it ain't gonna happen.
This is a Celestial Decree.
A Celestial Decree upon the Hyuuga Clan.
I will ask you one last time.
Answer me, Hyuuga Hiashi.
The answer, which will decide the future of your clan.
This is the Hyuuga's..
..reply!
You fool.
I'm gonna demonstrate some moves today.
Naruto-senpai!
I never expected him to become such high stakes material.
-Did you just say steak?
-High Stakes Popular with Girls.
His efforts in war two years ago.
Turned him into the village hero.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
All right, Eat up.
-Thank you
Naruto-niichan.
Hey, Konohamaru.
I have something to show you.
-What is it?
-It's Granpa Hiruzen stuff.
I found it during spring cleaning.
Hey, Is this?
Don't you dare call them junk.
They're really precious.
-These are.
-They're, not junk.
I'm Uzumaki Naruto.
Time sure flies.
Sale's for the Rinne Festival has already started.
Naruto-senpai.
Huh?
Please accept my Rinne Festival present.
For me?
I'm always cheering for you.
I made it myself.
-Please accept it.
H-Hey, Thanks.
Thank you very much.
Hinata.
Oh, Sakura-san.
Hmm?
Knitting something?
That's a surprise.
I'm making a scarf.
Hmm...
W-What is it?
Give it your all, okay?
Huh?
It's a present for him, right?
He's been really popular, lately.
Oh, really?
They even come all the way from other villages.
Just to take pictures of him.
Oh.
Don't say "oh"
Hurry up and finish that scarf.
Okay.
Come on, have more confidence.
Be bold.
O-Okay.
It looks a little big.
All done.
I put my heart and soul into it.
I'm sure my feelings will reach Naruto-kun.
But will they?
It's already late.
Maybe tomorrow's better.
Nope, I'll give it to him tonight.
Maybe tomorrow.
No, Tonight.
No, Tomorrow's
Just hurry up and tell him how you feel.
Hanabi.
Why didn't you say you we're there.
Watching a girl agonize over love is fun.
There's no way for a child to talk.
I'm not a child.
My Byakugan's perception is as good as any grown-up.
Anyway, look.
Isn't it cute?
Treating your kunai like a toy again.
He'll burst out laughing if your tummy growls while confessing your love.
I'm not going to confess anything.
Rather that giving him a scarf,
maybe you should make yourself look more fashionable.
The moon is falling.
The moon is clearly getting closer to earth.
Is that why there have been more meteorites lately?
I'll explain.
As two celestial bodies get closer to each other,
their gravity will began to pull.
Once a certain distance is reached.
The moon surface will begin to break apart.
I believe a part of the surface has begun to fall to earth.
And what will happen?
The moon will completely disintegrate.
And it's fragments will rain over the Earth's surface.
If nothing is done, mankind will...
Perish.
Is this a natural phenomenon?
Or is this a Man-made assault.
That's a good question.
It's getting to be the season when ramen really hits the spot.
You only eat ramen all year long.
You really like ramen, don't you?
Yup, I love it.
Five more orders of gyoza.
-Coming right up.
-Five more orders?
I can't eat that much.
Then don't have any.
Time to dig in-
Can't get this dirty.
Hey, That scarf.
Oh, Hinata.
Join us, If you haven't eaten.
It's on me tonight.
He said something made him happy and he wants to celebrate.
B-But...
Don't be shy, come and sit here.
Join us, Hinata.
O-Okay.
Naruto-senpai!
Hey, It's you guys.
Thanks for the presents the other day.
Order whatever you want.
It's my treat.
My thanks for the presents.
-Thank you so much.
Hinata, order what you want too.
-Over here, Senpai.
-Huh?
Let's eat together.
Hinata.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry
Actually, I'm quite full.
-Huh?
-Hinata.
Why don't you walk her home.
Walk Hinata home.
Why?
Well.
-You can't let a young girl
-Order up. Gyoza.
-Walk home alone at night.
-Thank you.
Huh. Hinata's really strong.
No one in the village would dare mess with her.
Hey.
Hinata.
Oh, you're such an idiot.
Why'd you call me an idiot?
Senpai, the gyoza is ready.
Let's eat.
He can be so dense.
You we're going to give him the scarf, right?
Uh-huh.
You can do it. Hinata.
Be confident.
Thanks.
But how come you're encouraging me so much.
Huh? Well...
We need to support each other.
Support each other?
Who's there?
That's Hanabi.
Chōjū Giga!
超獣偽画
(Chōjū Giga: "Super Beast Imitating Drawing ")
Naruto-kun.
I've always gazed at your back.
But from now on, I want to always.
Always stand by your side.
So, I knitted this with all my heart.
Please accept my feelings.
All right, one more time.
Naruto-kun.
Hinata.
Good evening.
We saw each other earlier at Ichiraku.
Oh, That's right.
What's the matter?
Th-That's a nice scarf.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, sounds like you're hungry.
If you don't mind instant ramen, I have some in my room.
Good night.
Didn't you want to talk to me?
Hey, Hinata.
I wonder who gave it to him.
I'm happy for you naruto.
Why are you crying?
You're getting the scarf wet.
I don't need it anymore.
Then I'll take it.
Who are you?
I'm Toneri.
I've come for you.
Come for me?
-Hinata!
-What, let me go.
Bastard, what are you doing to Hinata?
Tajū Kage Bunshin no Jutsu!
多重影分身の術
(Tajū Kage Bunshin no Jutsu: "Multiple Shadow Clone Technique ")
Hinata.
Rasenshuriken!
螺旋手裏剣
(Rasenshuriken: "Spiralling Shuriken")
Why you.
Let Hinata go.
Hold it!
Hinata, Are you okay?
Yeah.
Rasengan!
螺旋丸
(Rasengan: "Spiralling Sphere")
My body is going numb.
My strength...
Hinata!
Your scarf's ruined.
Yes.
Where'd those shinobi come from?
I don't know
The final day is approaching.
Before that...
You bastard!
Before that day, I will come for you.
Hinata.
What is that?
W-What's going on?
The Earth..
..will be destroyed, soon.
Your mission is to.
Rescue Hyuga Hanabi who has been kidnapped.
You'll be working as a 4-man team led by Shikamaru.
I'm also granting Hinata's wish to be included in this team.
Thank you very much.
Shikamaru, put your hand out!
Huh?
Why?
What's this?
A top secret clock that only five kage possess.
What kind of clock is it?
It's counting down the time until the Earth's destruction.
I don't get it.
Why's this necessary for Hanabi's rescue.
Toneri, the one who kidnapped Hanabi,
could be the one manipulating the moon.
What are you basing this on?
It's just a hunch.
It was around here..
..that I lost sight of Hanabi's kidnapper.
Let's split up and search for clues.
Naruto, take care of Hinata.
Leave it to me.
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
-Oh.
-What is it?
It's Hanabi's kunai.
Hmm, you brought the scarf?
Huh?
Why aren't you using it?
Aren't you cold?
I-I'm fine.
Anyways, we'd better hurry and let Shikamaru and the others know.
Oh, yeah. You're right.
What do you see Hinata?
There's a spring that glowing at the bottom of the cave.
A spring that's glowing?
That shinobi letter is "A" as in Aun.
It could mean "This is the beginning"
Hinata, what can you see at the bottom of the spring?
My vision is distorted.
Your Byakugan is distorting?
Well, just have to go down and see.
Whoa, I can't get this wet.
You're so particular.
What's the big deal if your scarf got wet?
It's a big deal. This means a lot to me.
Huh?
There is nothing to worry about.
I touched this water and I didn't get wet.
If the world were to end tomorrow,
who would you like to spend your last day with?
Like that would happen?
Just suppose the moon began to fall.
If it's the end of the world.
I wish meat would fall instead of the moon.
Look, the moon!
Huh?
The match-up for round 7.
Uzumaki Naruto versus..
..Inuzuka Kiba.
This is the chunin exam.
Naruto.
Don't you dare lose to a guy like him.
Gijū Ninpō: Shikyaku no Jutsu!
擬獣忍法:四脚の術
(Gijū Ninpō: Shikyaku no Jutsu: "Imitation Beast Ninja Art: Four Legs Technique")
Wait a minute!
Here I come.
Stop it, Kiba.
Naruto-kun is fighting pain right now.
Naruto-kun is fighting alone.
Banshō Ten'in!
万象天引
(Banshō Ten'in: "Heavenly Attraction of All Creation")
Naruto-kun.
What is it?
It's ointment.
Why're you giving it to me?
Just accept it, Naruto.
Thank you, you're so kind, Hinata.
Banshō Ten'in!
万象天引
(Banshō Ten'in: "Heavenly Attraction of All Creation")
You're about to be captured now.
Why'd you come out here?
You're no match for him.
This time.
I'm going to save you, Naruto-kun.
I was always crying and giving up before even trying.
I made so many mistakes.
But, you helped me find my way and take the correct path, Naruto-kun.
I always chased after you.
I wanted to walk beside you all the time.
I want to be at your side, Always.
You changed me, Naruto-kun.
Your smile is what saved me.
That's why, I'm not afraid to die..
..if it means I can protect you.
Because..
I love you, Naruto-kun.
Hinata.
If the world were to end tomorrow,
who would you like to spend the last day with?
If it's the end of the world,
I wish meat would fall instead of the moon.
Not Iruka-sensei again.
Write down who'd you want to spend your last day on Earth with.
Hey, Naruto.
Don't throw out you paper.
But, there's no way that the world's gonna end.
I'm just saying "if" it does.
Well it ain't gonna happen.
"Uzumaki Naruto"
Huh? Me?
Naruto-kun.
What is it?
It's ointment.
Why're you giving it to me?
-So dense.
-Huh?
He can be so dense.
You were going to give him that scarf, weren't you?
Uh-Huh.
You can do it, Hinata.
Be confident.
Thanks.
Naruto-kun, I...
You really like ramen, don't you?
Yup, I love it.
Naruto-kun, I...
You really like.
Yup, I love Hinata.
He's so dense.
Maybe he doesn't know what love is.
What do you mean?
Like knowing the difference between loving sweets,
like shiratama dumplings and fruit gelatin and love.
Huh, They're not the same?
Hinata.
Oh, you're such and idiot.
Why'd you call me an idiot?
Senpai, the gyoza are ready.
Let's eat.
-Hinata.
-Oh.
Senpai!
Hinata!
"Uzumaki Naruto"
Hinata.
That's why I'm not afraid to die..
..if it means I can protect you.
Because, Naruto-kun..
I love you.
Hinata.
Naruto.
Wake up.
This is a dream.
Oh, Sakura-chan.
You're finally awake.
Is this a trap set by the enemy?
Yeah, it traps intruders in a Genjutsu.
And shuts them away in a world of memories.
It's a prison of caged memories.
Thank goodness Sakura who's resistant to Genjutsu was with us.
Thanks, Sakura..
..for breaking a fun dream with my big brother apart.
That doesn't sound like gratitude.
Another spring?
Your Byakugan doesn't work here either?
No, my field of sight is distorted.
All right, be ready to fight as we proceed.
-Roger.
What's the matter?
About those Ginjutsu dreams earlier.
What is it?
No, never mind.
Hinata.
I said I'd come for you..
..to have you come to me.
Where is Hanabi?
Don't worry.
She's fast asleep in my castle.
Return Hanabi.
That will all depend on your answer.
Byakugan Princess.
Byakugan Princess?
Hinata, let's get married.
Huh? marry?
It's like a bubble factory.
I get it.
Huh?
This is were the gatekeeper who made the bubbles lives.
Gatekeeper?
Naruto and Hinata are late.
Should we go back to check?
A-A crab?
That's the gatekeeper.
Hinata.
Naruto-kun.
Don't get near Hinata.
You again. You're in the way. Move!
Where is Hanabi?
Don't destroy the bubbles.
Or we'll get caught by the Genjutsu again.
Chōjū Giga!
超獣偽画
(Chōjū Giga: "Super Beast Imitating Drawing")
Fujin. Raijin.
Damn it.
Kage Nui!
影縫い
(Kage Nui: "Shadow Sewing")
Sakura.
Shannaro!
(Shannaro: "A word that always shouts out by Sakura when she's pissed or extremely excited, could be used as "Alright, damnit!" or "F*ck yeah!")
Damn it.
You're a puppet?
This is not my body.
Hinata.
Next time, the real me will come for you.
Give me an answer then.
Shut up!
Your fist will never reach me, never.
Did your punch do this, Sakura-chan?
Oh, Yeah.
Naruto, if you leave Hinata behind and expose her to danger again,
you'll get a taste of my fists too.
I know.
Hinata, I'll never let you..
I'll never let you out of my sight again.
What?
You're already looking away.
Huh, I'm not looking away.
What is this place?
Is that island floating?
No.
The surface of the ocean is warped.
There's sunlight underground too.
Isn't that a fake?
An artificial sun?
Yeah.
Hinata, any sign of the enemy?
No, we're good.
The enemy is aware of us.
Why aren't they attacking?
Yeah, that bothers me.
It's too quiet.
Leave them.
Don't do anything until I go to get her.
Oh..
the eyes are twitching again.
Amazing, this Byakugan is very pure.
Hinata?
That scarf, seriously is it for me?
I see a town about 20 kilos ahead.
All right, let's go.
There's no one here.
This town was built a few centuries ago.
Let's split up and search.
So, it's a shinobi village.
A fire?
What is this?
Was there a war long ago?
What's wrong? Hinata?
It's a spider web.
You can see far with your Byakugan,
but you walk straight to the spider web.
You're so silly.
Naruto-kun.
What is it?
What happened to your scarf?
Oh.
It's warm underground, So I took it off.
I-I see.
I feel a bit cold.
I'll bet you are, dressed like that.
It's just that, this is my mission gear.
If you can take it,
I can handle a little cold like this.
Are you okay?
I'm totally fine.
What?
It's nothing.
What is it?
I said, it's nothing.
Tell me.
That was so good.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm gonna take a leak.
Naruto-kun.
A spider web.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Ow.
What's wrong?
I think I hurt my back.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Oh yeah,
you gave me some ointment back during chuunin exams.
You remembered all this time.
Actually, I just remembered.
Thanks.
We have to hurry and rescue Hanabi.
Naruto-kun, I'd like to talk to you about something.
What is it?
About what you said when that puppet Toneri appeared.
Toneri?
Here they are.
Hinata, we need you to check something.
What's it say?
It's some ancient writing.
Ancient oath.
Crossing the path of humanity.
Like all else.
The fist of the Tensei eye the reborn moon,
will destroy man.
What does that mean?
Maybe the "Tensei Eye" is making the moon move.
So, Kakashi-sensei was right?
Hanabi's abduction and the moon are somehow connected.
Well, his hunches are always on target unfortunately.
Byakugan Princess.
What's that?
Is this a burial site?
What's this?
Someone's here.
The Byakugan. I sense the Byakugan.
Oh, I'm certain of it.
Oh, Byakugan Princess.
Stay away from Hinata.
Hinata.
What did you do to Hinata?
The Tenseigan has revived.
It must be stopped.
Otsutsuki.
Hinata, are you all right?
Uh-huh.
That man said something like Otsutsuki.
That's the original surname of the Sage of Six Paths.
That was the name of the Sage of Six Paths, before he entered the priesthood.
And he called Hinata the Byakugan Princess.
Otsutsuki Hagoromo.
Seems Toneri's abduction of Hanabi is connected.
Knitting.
Is she going to keep knitting forever?
I guess it takes a lot of time.
Hinata, what was it that you wanted to talk about earlier?
You mentioned something about what Toneri's puppet said?
Oh, that.
It was nothing.
Huh? What did you mean nothing?
I'm sorry, I want to be alone.
I see.
Let's check out that village.
Seems like Hanabi's not here anymore.
We should head back and rejoin the others.
Uh-huh.
Hinata.
My younger sister is in so much danger,
and here I'm knitting.
I'm a terrible big sister, aren't I?
That's not true.
You've come all this way just to save your sister.
I'm sure if I stayed at home then Hanabi will be safe.
Don't worry, I swear I will rescue Hanabi.
Thank you.
You're so kind, Naruto-kun.
Hey, I'm not just being kind because I love you or anything.
I'm just worried about Hanabi.
-What did you just say?
-Huh?
Did you say something?
I'm worried about Hanabi.
Before that...
Before that is..
Hinata..
I... love you.
Hinata.
Toneri, are you another puppet?
Where is Hanabi?
Silence!
I came to hear Hinata's answer.
Answer? Hinata has nothing to say to you!
So, Where's Hanabi?
Hinata.
Hey.
Hinata, what's going on?
Good-bye, Naruto-kun.
Huh?
Hinata.
Give Hinata back.
Give her back?
Hinata came to me willingly.
This has been destined.
Since ancient times.
Hinata and I shall be married.
M-Marry?
Hinata.
That's a lie, right?
My chakra is...
What are you doing?
I don't want to get into a petty fight.
And risk getting you hurt.
Hinata.
Hurry up and go.
I can't go any further.
Hey, stay in line.
Don't panic.
The air raid shelter was constructed..
..to accommodate every citizen in the Land of Fire.
Keep calm.
Please keep calm.
Suiton: Suiryūdan!
水遁:水龍弾
(Suiton: Suiryūdan: "Water Release: Water Dragon Bullet")
Yōton: Yōkai no Jutsu!
溶遁:溶怪の術
(Yōton: Yōkai no Jutsu: "Lava Release: Melting Apparition Technique")
Jinton: Genkai Hakuri no Jutsu!
塵遁:原界剥離の術
(Jinton: Genkai Hakuri no Jutsu: "Dust Release: Detachment of the Primitive World Technique")
Damn it, my back.
So, this was the moon?
Yeah.
The space where we found the crab's bubbles..
..is probably the passage way that connects the earth to the moon.
How is Naruto doing?
Terrible.
Most of his chakra has been sucked out.
Hinata.
So you finally get it.
You blockhead.
So beautiful.
Hinata, I want to know more about you.
Why him?
Where am I?
This is, Toneri's castle.
Hanabi.
Hanabi's eyes have been taken.
Hinata.
Let's get married.
Huh? Married?
What are you saying?
Let Hanabi.
Your sister is in my castle.
Hanabi.
I've taken her Byakugan.
You're terrible.
I'm sorry.
It's due to Hamura's Celestial Decree.
Hamura?
Otsutsuki Hamura,
The founder of the Shinobi of the Moon.
Perhaps, It's easier to understand if i say he's the younger brother
of the Sage of Six Paths, founder of the Shinobi of Earth.
Your Hyuuga Clan inherited Hamura's blood.
The story goes back many eons.
Several millenia, in fact.
The Sage of Six Paths, the elder one, had misgivings.
He feared that the Ten Tails..
..with it's massive chakra and immeasurable power..
..would bring calamity to the world.
So, The Sage of Six Paths extracted the Ten Tails Chakra..
..and divided it among nine Tailed Beasts in order to weaken it's power.
The Husk of the Ten Tails whose chakra was extracted..
..namely the Gedo Statue, was hidden away and sealed on the moon.
So that the Ten Tails would never be revived.
Hamura decided to live on the moon..
..in order to guard the Gedo statue.
The Sage of Six Paths became the founder of the Shinobi of Earth.
But, Hamura was skeptical of the world..
..his elder brother was creating.
So, If the world created by his brother went astray from the Shinobi way..
He entrusted his descendants with its destruction..
..through the millenia that has passed.
Fighting between Shinobi has not ceased,
they continue to use chakra as a weapon.
Ultimately, The Gedo Statue was stolen,
and even the Ten Tails was revived.
Our Clan has reached the conclusion..
..that the Shinobi of Earth will destroy the world's peace and order.
The world that the Sage of Six Paths created is a failure.
So, in accordance with the Celestial Decree of Hamura
I will destroy the world of the Sage of Six Paths.
When this pure Byakugan synergizes with my chakra,
it will transform into Tenseigan.
With it's visual prowess, I will pick up the ashes of Earth..
..and create a new world.
I don't believe your story.
And I'm going to rescue Hanabi.
Even when you don't know where the castle is located?
I'll return for you answer.
Hinata.
Good morning.
I'm happy that you understand how I feel, Hinata.
Hinata-sama, welcome to the castle.
-Welcome
-Welcome.
There are only puppets in this castle.
They're marionettes left here by our ancestors.
Since my father died when I was young,
I've lived in the castle all by myself.
We will hold the marriage ceremony here.
Then we will enter the Room of Rebirth..
..and fall into a deep slumber..
..until the Earth's environment stabilizes after its destruction,
That's impossible.
The moon will also be destroyed.
Don't worry, this castle is protected by a strong chakra.
Is that chakra really that strong?
Yes, strong enough to move the moon.
What do you mean?
It's the power of Otsutsuki's treasure..
..honed from the sufferings of my clan.
Where would such a thing be?
That is something..
..I cannot tell you.
May I return to my room?
It's cold outside.
That's because It's dusk here all year.
Oh, That's right.
Will you knit me a scarf?
Huh?
A scarf just for me.
Do you refuse?
I understand.
Really? Thank you.
You've made me happy, Hinata.
What's wrong?
Don't worry.
It's proof that the Byakugan is maturing into the Tenseigan.
It will subside with a little rest.
It doesn't seem to be here.
Byakugan Princess.
Tenseigan, activate.
We are descendants of Hamura.
We belong to the main family of the Otsutsuki Clan.
We were annihilated by the branch family..
..who was twisted the interception of Hamura's Celestial Decree.
Toneri, a descendant of the branch family is attempting to make the moon..
..fall into the earth using the power of the Tenseigan.
Only you can destroy the Tenseigan, Byakugan Princess.
You are Otsutsuki Hamura.
Byakugan Princess.
Do not let the world my elder brother created come to an end.
Hanabi, You poor thing.
I'll definitely find and destroy..
The Tenseigan.
Imagine that..
Toneri has been hiding in the artificial sun.
Why hasn't Hinata's Byakugan able to discover it?
Maybe, he has a jutsu on the artificial sun that deflects the Byakugan too?
Where's the entrance?
Why don't we ask them?
What are you doing?
You've alerted the enemy.
Follow me.
What are you doing?
I'll explain later.
So, is that how it is.
Sai, Retreat.
Chōjū Giga!
超獣偽画
(Chōjū Giga: "Super Beast Imitating Drawing")
I never imagined that his turn to appear would come after the war,
when the world was peaceful.
Beneath is the chakra Diffusion Cannon.
We'll blast all the meteorites above the equator.
On top is the chakra Transportation Cannon..
..it can transport any target into another dimension.
With these we'll destroy the moon.
Everyone, get the cannons ready immediately.
Meals are nice when you have someone to talk to.
Now, tell me all about yourself.
It's not too late to negotiate with the shinobi of Earth.
What?
You're right.
The Shinobi of Earth have used chakra..
..and continued fighting.
But, it's different now.
In order to protect this hard-fought peace,
shinobi have joined together.
So...
They will start another war.
The Sage of Six Paths' world must be destroyed.
But...
Never bring up that subject again.
Now be quiet and eat.
That island.
So, it's appeared already.
This is the Temple of the Hamura.
Once a year, during the Rebirth Festival it comes near the castle.
I'm sure of it.
The Tenseigan is hidden on that island.
Good-bye, Naruto-kun.
Hinata.
You're finally awake.
Finally?
It's been three days.
Huh?
Did something happen between you and Hinata?
No, not really.
You kept groaning her name.
Hinata, Hinata.
As well as some other embarassing things.
But, I got to listen in on your mushy side.
It was such great research material for me.
Come on.
Naruto.
Let's go rescue Hinata and Hanabi.
Is it hard to see the woman who dumped you?
So, Naruto's strong as a Shinobi but he can't handle a broken heart.
Now, I know your weakness.
Hey.
Hamura must be happy that you personally want to play homage.
The Tenseigan is inside here.
This is...
The Tenseigan.
Then this is Otsutsuki's treasure that is moving the moon?
Hinata-sama, only those in exalted positions..
..are allowed to see the real Tenseigan.
This is a temple where others of lower rank come to pray.
I see.
I shall show you the real Tenseigan after we are married.
My field of vision is distorted only at that spot.
I see, I get it.
How long are you going to be like that?
You gave up on a woman..
So, why not giving up on becoming a Hokage too?
Yeah, give it up.
Give up on the woman as well as becoming Hokage.
What? Shikamaru?
Are you picking a fight?
I don't care what happens between you and Hinata.
But you're a Shinobi.
Huh?
Come with me.
I'm going to my room to rest.
I'm looking forward to the finished scarf.
I feel it, I can feel it.
The beating in my eyes.
It will be born very soon.
The complete Tenseigan.
Sakura-chan.
It's the result of infusing nearly every ounce of her chakra into you..
..so that she could prevent you from dying.
Sakura-chan.
Naruto.
Sakura-chan, I'm so sorry.
Are you going to depend on Sakura to heal not only his body..
..but his heart as well?
Can you do it?
You have a point.
I see.
I never thought you'd confess your love first.
Remember long ago, when you said you love me?
But, wasn't that because I love Sasuke-kun?
You didn't want to lose to him.
It's real this time, Isn't it?
Hinata, is a great person.
She's almost too good for you.
But, it's over.
Hinata, went to Toneri.
You are so stupid.
It's obvious that she had a reason that she couldn't reveal.
When a girl truly falls in love,
her feelings don't change so easily.
They can't change.
I understand how she feels very well.
This is..
The Tenseigan.
I'll stop the moon.
What's going on?
You're wrong.
What?
Hamura's soul entrusted me with the Celestial Decree.
You have distorted Hamura's teachings.
Hamura never wished for the destruction of Earth..
..The Sage of Six Path's world.
You've betrayed me.
Please hear me out. Hamura is...
Silence!
They're lies.
I don't believe it.
There is only one Celestial Decree that Hamura made.
That is to end the world of the Sage of Six Paths.
Damn it.
So, you were knitting this..
..for him and not me?
I'm going to make it so.
You'll never betray me again.
Hinata.
This big idiot finally understands.
The meaning of the scarf you gave me when you went to Toneri.
I know now, from the scarf you painstakingly knitted..
..and took so long to finish.
That your love can't be unraveled so easily.
Naruto-kun.
Wait for me.
You've love someone like me forever and ever.
Now, as a man, there's something I've got to say to you.
Hinata, I swear I'm gonna save you.
Raikage-sama, the chakra Cannons are ready.
All right.
Men, load the chakra!
-Yes, Sir.
First, We'll fire the chakra Diffusion Cannon to pulverize the meteorites.
Pulverize, powderize.
I need assistance.
You got it.
Rasenshuriken!
螺旋手裏剣
(Rasenshuriken: "Spiralling Shuriken")
Kageshibari no Jutsu!
影縛りの術
(Kageshibari no Jutsu: "Shadow Bind Technique")
Next.
We're storming the citadel.
Right.
Sakura-chan.
Thanks, Naruto.
No need to thank me.
I have a debt to you that I'll never be able to repay.
What a drag.
Why hide it?
It's irritating, and prevents me from making wise decisions.
Naruto, can you sense Hanabi's chakra?
Hanabi is in that tower over there.
Sakura, Sai.
Take care of Hanabi.
-Okay
-Okay.
Hinata.
You bastard.
Your fist will never reach me.
Naruto, where's Hinata?
In there.
I'll handle things here.
Thanks.
Move.
Whoa, I won't let you pass.
All right, the puppet show begins now.
Hanabi is above here.
What?
This way.
Hinata.
Fūton: Kūsa Bōheki!
風遁:空砂防壁
(Fūton: Kūsa Bōheki: "Wind Release: Air Sand Protective Wall")
At six o'clock. It's a huge one.
Everyone, Kakuyoku no Jin!
鶴翼の陣
(Kakuyoku no Jin: "Crane Wing Formation")
-Roger
-Roger.
Dai Roku Keimon!
大六景門
(Dai Roku Keimon: "The Gate of Joy")
Damn it!
You're...
If he's not around..
..the only one who can protect the village..
..is me.
Sasuke.
The meteorites are gone.
Hokage-sama.
What is it?
Hiashi-san.
Chakra capacity at 75%
76,77
One after the other.
Go in.
Hinata.
What did you do?
Give Hinata back.
Fine, I shall give her back to you.
Stop, Hinata.
What do you think of my wife's skills?
Damn it.
He's controlling her.
Hinata.
Bear with it for just a while.
Don't you dare manipulate Hinata.
Hinata belongs to me.
I'm taking her back.
Hinata.
Be gone.
Bastard.
It's too early to wake up.
Damn.
The final pulsation.
Naruto-kun.
Hinata.
I'm so sorry, Naruto-kun. I...
I understand.
So don't say anything.
I'm the one who has to apologize.
But, what about him?
Now's our chance.
We have to destroy the Tenseigan.
Tenseigan?
Hanabi.
How terrible.
She's just a child.
Hinata.
If we destroy this, the moon should stop it's approach.
Got it, I'll use my Rasengan.
No!
There is a cursed jutsu cast upon this eye.
Only someone with Hamura's blood can touch it,
anyone else will get their chakra extracted.
What?
Hakke: Sōjishi Hōgeki!
八卦:双獅子崩撃
(Hakke: Sōjishi Hōgeki: "Eight Trigrams: Twin Lions Crumbling Attack")
I can't destroy it.
Hinata, Infuse me with your chakra.
Huh?
Then we might be able to break it apart.
Let's go.
Okay.
(Info: This technique is Gentle Step Spiralling Twin Lion Fists ^_^)
These are...
The Tenseigan was a cluster of Byakugan?
What?
Hokage-sama.
The moon has stopped it's approach.
What?
Chakra capacity at 95%
96,97,98,99
Chakra is at 100%
Chakra Diffusion Cannon. Fire!
Yeah.
What just happened?
An urgent message from the Cloud Village.
A Five Kage Summit is being convened
All the meteorites have been destroyed.
So, you had a weapon like that hidden away?
It seems we cannot be too careful with you, Raikage.
Tsuchikage-sama, let's forget the sarcasm.
Next up is the chakra Transportation Cannon.
We'll blow up the moon.
Blow up the moon?
What's happening?
Shikamaru.
Hinata, are you all right?
Yes, I'm sorry.
Save that for later.
Anyway, what happened?
The artificial sun disappeared.
We destroyed the Tenseigan.
It was the source of power for everything.
The moon should have stop moving too.
What?
The treasure that my entire clan offered their eyes to..
..the Otsutsuki treasure..
..how dare they.
Hanabi.
Thank you.
This is yours, right?
Uh-huh.
Isn't that the scarf that Toneri ripped off.
How did you know?
When I pulled Toneri's jutsu in you body.
I was able to see your memories.
You were going to give it to Naruto, Right?
Did you make it for me?
U-Uh-huh.
Can I have it?
But, It's in shreds.
I don't care.
I mean, I want it.
Thank you.
I'll cherish it.
Naruto-kun.
What's the matter?
The clock..
..it's moving.
-Huh
With these eyes, Naruto.
I'll destroy your world.
It's too dangerous to blow up the moon.
As long as there's a bomb called the moon,
The earth will be not safe.
Now, let's discuss this calmly.
Right now, the moon has stopped it's approached.
No, It hasn't stopped.
What?
Why is the clock ticking again?
I don't know.
W-What was that?
Kurama!
It's Toneri.
Ginrin Tensei Baku!
銀輪転生爆
(Ginrin Tensei Baku: "Silver Wheel Reincarnation Explosion")
Chakra capacity at 90%
Hokage-sama.
Hiashi-san would like a word with you.
Hiashi-san?
Don't destroy the moon.
I'm certain that Hanabi and Hinata are on the moon.
What do you mean by that?
Bad news.
What is it?
The Nine Tails is on the moon's surface.
What?
Chakra capacity at 95%
Raikage-sama, an urgent message from Hokage-sama.
What does he want at a critical time?
Please hold the Chakra Cannon.
Naruto and the others are at the moon.
It can't be helped.
They have to be sacrificed for the sake of the humanity and the earth.
We're going to fire the Chakra Transportation Cannon.
-Raikage-dono.
-What is it?
I'm asking you too. Wait one hour.
What?
I agree.
Mizukage.
Naruto is the hero of the last great war.
He's worth betting on.
Tsuchikage.
Just one hour will do.
But for them, that amount of time will be a worth a lifetime..
..that can never be replaced.
What do you based that on?
My hunch.
Hinata, are you okay?
Uh-huh.
No.
I'm taking Hinata back.
You can watch his last moments, from there.
Hinata.
Naruto-kun.
The world created by the Sage of Six Paths is a failure.
I'm destroying both the earth and you.
I won't let the earth get destroyed.
Rasenrangan!
螺旋乱丸
(Rasenrangan: "Spiralling Strife Spheres")
Kinrin Tensei Baku!
金輪転生爆
(Kinrin Tensei Baku: "Golden Wheel Reincarnation Explosion")
Naruto-kun.
What is that?
The moon..
..the moon has split apart.
What?
What's happening?
Hey, Hokage?
There's only ten minutes left.
He's done.
I'm not done yet.
Chōōdama Rasen Tarengan!
超大玉螺旋多連丸
(Chōōdama Rasen Tarengan: "Many Ultra-Big Ball Spiralling Serial Spheres")
It's useless, give it up.
Like, I'd give up.
It takes time to knit a scarf.
The deeper the feelings you want to convey..
..the longer it takes to knit.
It's over now.
Like I'd let you.
To convey one's feelings..
..it takes much, much, much, more time.
That's why..
..I can't let it end, So easily!
You got me with, one punch.
The Tenseigan is fading.
Huh?
Hinata.
Naruto-kun.
I'm taking back Hanabi's eyes.
No. Stop!
Why you?
This is over.
Not yet.
Sakura, are you okay?
What about Naruto and the others?
I don't know.
W-What's going on?
I'll end it all with these eyes.
Kugutsu Tensei!
傀儡転生
(Kugutsu Tensei: "Puppet Reincarnation")
You're annoying.
Naruto.
Hinata.
Toneri, please stop it already.
All you did was follow your ancestor's misguided teachings.
Quiet!
As the last survivor of the Otsutsuki Clan.
I must fulfill Hamura's Celestial Decree.
Naruto-kun.
All my chakra's being sucked out.
You'll know feel the power of Hamura,
one that you can even move the moon.
Naruto, it's over for you.
Hinata?
What?
I won't let it end yet.
Why?
Hamura's chakra flows within me too.
Stop it already!
End it! The world of the Sage of Six Paths.
I will destroy the Sage's world, that has fallen into darkness..
..with the light of justice.
What?
His jutsu absorbed the sun's energy..
..and now he's passed his chakra limits.
Naruto-kun.
Don't, it's too dangerous!
Time's up.
Fire the chakra Transportation Cannon!
What's wrong?
I can't shoot at Naruto.
Stifle your personal feelings.
The very existence of Earth depends on this.
Move, I'll fire it!
Raikage-sama, there is some writing on the moon.
What?
Kurama is writing something on the moon's surface.
That Shinobi letter means..
..mission accomplished.
The mission was successful!
I see.
Every announcement to the entire world!
The moon has stopped.
Thanks to the efforts of these five..
..Shikamaru, Sakura, Sai, Hinata, and Naruto,
the future of Earth is safe.
My hunches usually end on a high note.
Making me write the letters..
I'm bad at caligraphy.
Sorry, Kurama.
T-This is...
Hamura's soul guided me here.
Toneri, everyone on Earth will welcome you.
I will remain on the moon and atone for my sins.
Toneri.
One day, one day..
come to Earth.
The moon will never approach Earth.
Never again.
Naruto-kun, there's something I have to ask you.
What is it?
T-That scarf..
..who gave it to you?
Oh, this?
My late mom made it for me?
What?
My Grandpa must've kept it for her.
Mom.
I see.
I'm so silly.
Hey, Onee-sama!
How long are you going to chit-chat? I'm going on ahead of you.
Hurry up, the passageway is starting to disintegrate.
Let's go home to Earth.
Yes.
Hinata.
Yes?
Back in school..
..when we were asked who we'd want to spend your last day on Earth with?
I couldn't write anyone's name down.
I didn't know my parents, and I didn't have any friends.
But now,
I know exactly who'd I'd choose.
I want to stay with you.
Now and forever, until I die..
..I want to be with you, Hinata.
Naruto-kun.
Hinata, put your arms around me.
Huh?
O-Okay.
Don't let it go, okay?
I won't.
I'll never, ever let it go.
Huh? What are you doing?
Onee-sama.
Naruto, you're going to crash into the ceiling.
Like I'm going to let it stop here.
Hinata.
Naruto-kun.
Thank you, Hinata.
doushite doushite naite umarete
itsuka nakarete hoshi ni natteikundarou
bokura wa doushite doushite osowattenai noni
namida no nagashikata wa shitterundarou
afureru shizuku wa taema naku
sosogareta aijou no akashi de
michibikareru mama yuruyaka ni sotto tsutattekitanda
kokoro kara karada e karada wa kokoro e
tsuranaru ikutsumo no karamiatta rasen no moyou
sono hitotsu hitotsu ni mirai ga mieta nara
nagameteiru kono sora mo
hora uchuu ni mieru
doushite doushite tsuki wa itsudemo
nanimo iwanaide yami o terashiteirundarou
bokura wa doushite doushite kodou no kazu ni
kagiri ga aru tte no o shitteite muda ni shichaundarou
mune ni kakaeteiru utsuwa no
ookisa ni kachi o midasunjanakute
sono naka ni aru netsu o obita tane ni inochi o kanjitai
donna ni me o korashite jibun o miyou to shitemo
boyakete yoku mienai ya sono uchi miushinatteshimau
sagaseba sagasu hodo chirakashiteshimau nara
miyoumimane datte kono te de
sou tsukureba ii
ikiru tte iu koto sore wa kitto
sukoshizutsu tebanashiteiku koto
saigo no hitotsu o ushinau sono toki
soba ni ite
namida o kureru hito ga iru
sore de ureshii
kokoro kara karada e karada wa kokoro e
tsuranaru ikutsumo no uketsugu rasen no moyou
kurikaesareteku koto ga eien dato omoeta toki
me no mae no keshiki subete ga
ima, uchuu ni natta
uchuu ni natta
Why, oh why, are we born crying,
Then someday made to cry again, before we go on to become stars.
Why, oh why, though we weren't ever taught.
Do we know how to shed tears?
The drops that well up are
an unending symbol of lavished love.
As they are led along, they make themselves known softly, gently.
From heart to body, as body becomes heart,
With all the many intertwined spiral formations involved.
If we can see the future in each and every one,
even this sky we're gazing upon
Will seem as part of the cosmos.
Why, oh why, does the moon,
Never say a thing as it illuminates the darkness.
Why, oh why, though we know there's a limit to our heartbeats,
Do we still spend them wastefully?
Rather than trying to assign value
based on the size of the vessels we hold in our chests,
I'd rather try to feel the life coming from the warmed seeds within.
No matter how much we squint our eyes, trying to see ourselves,
It'll still be too blurry to make out, until we lose track of it completely.
If the more we search, the more it will fall to pieces,
even acts of imitation,
Yes, are better off created by our own hands.
What it means to live life, surely,
is to let go little by little.
Then at the moment you lose your last,
there's someone by your side
to give you their tears.
With that alone, we're happy.
From heart to body, as body becomes heart,
With all the many inherited spiral formations involved.
From the moment we perceived of this repetition as eternity,
all of the scenery before our eyes,
Now, became part of the cosmos.
Became part of the cosmos.
どうしてどうして泣いて生まれて
いつか泣かれて星になっていくんだろう
僕らはどうしてどうして教わってないのに
涙の流し方は知ってるんだろう
溢れる雫は絶え間なく
注がれた愛情の証で
導かれるままゆるやかにそっと伝ってきたんだ
こころからからだへからだはこころへ
連なるいくつもの絡み合ったらせんの模様
そのひとつひとつに未来が見えたなら
眺めているこの空も
ほら宇宙に見える
どうしてどうして月はいつでも
何も言わないで闇を照らしているんだろう
僕らはどうしてどうして鼓動の数に
限りがあるってのを知っていてムダにしちゃうんだろう
胸に抱えている器の
大きさに価値を見出すんじゃなくて
その中にある熱を帯びたタネに“生命(いのち)”を感じたい
どんなに眼を凝らして自分を見ようとしても
ぼやけてよく見えないやそのうち見失ってしまう
探せば探すほど散らかしてしまうなら
見様見真似だってこの手で
そう作ればいい
生きるっていうことそれはきっと
少しずつ手放していくこと
最後の一つを失うその時
そばにいて
涙をくれる人がいる
それで嬉しい
こころからからだへからだはこころへ
連なるいくつもの受け継ぐらせんの模様
繰り返されてくことが永遠だと思えた時
目の前の景色すべてが
いま、宇宙になった
宇宙になった
Daddy.
Play with us.
Hey, don't go outside in your bare feet!
All right, Boruto, Himawari.
How about a snowball fight?
-A Snowball fight
Take that.
Hey, Boruto.
All right, you asked for it.
-Yay
-Yay.
Hey, you know when mom getting serious, She's super strong.